W.A.C. Bennett fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Ephemera (MLA), 1941 - 1952; F-55-26; 39 cm of textual records
  - Legislative Session - Pamphlet, 1945; F-55-26-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-40)
  - Legislative Session - Pamphlets, resolution, proposals, notes, financial statistics, 1946; F-55-26-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-40)
  - Legislative Session - Press releases, reports, minutes, 1950; F-55-26-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-40)
  - Legislative Session - Minutes, memoranda, statistics, proposals, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-40)
  - Legislative Session - Briefs, proposals, statistics, memoranda, reports, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-40)
  - Legislative Session - Statements, resolutions, briefs, proposals, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-40)
  - Legislative Session - Letters (mimeographed), statistics, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Legislative Session, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Legislative Session, 1952; F-55-26-0-0-12.1 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1942; F-55-26-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1944; F-55-26-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1945; F-55-26-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1945; F-55-26-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1946; F-55-26-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1946; F-55-26-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1947; F-55-26-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1948; F-55-26-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1949; F-55-26-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1950; F-55-26-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Premier--Press Releases, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Kelowna Capital News, 1941 - 1950; F-55-26-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Markets Bulletin, 1947 - 1951; F-55-26-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Vancouver Board of Trade - Manual, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Miscellaneous, 1941; F-55-26-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Miscellaneous, 1942; F-55-26-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 55-41)
  - Miscellaneous, 1943; F-55-26-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952; F-55-26-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1944; F-55-26-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1945; F-55-26-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1946; F-55-26-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1947; F-55-26-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1948; F-55-26-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1949; F-55-26-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950; F-55-26-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950; F-55-26-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1951; F-55-26-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, 1952; F-55-26-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
  - Miscellaneous, F-55-26-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 55-42)
- 1952 Official files, 1948 - 1972; F-55-27; 32 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened in 1952. Included are correspondence with the Social Credit constituency associations and elected Social Credit and C.C.F. Members (years are cumulated), file notes, statistics, financial statements and speeches.
  - Alberni Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (1-5) - Letters, telegrams, newsletters, card. Letters from: H. Law, Clara Sexton, W.J. Morissette, Gustav Frigstad, D.P. Russell, David G. Galliford, Kathleen Pickles, Hilda Hastings, 1952 - 1967; F-55-27-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Alberni Member--Stanley John Squire (CCF) (1-5) - Letters, file notes. Letters from: Stanley John Squire, 1954 - 1966; F-55-27-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Burnaby Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (4-4) - Letters. Letters from: C.F. Stelter, A.C. Waugh, J.A. Middleton, T.R. Collings, Edward Trotter, R.E. Arnold, Austin Hanna, J.P. Hollingworth, G. Nutall, J.C. Hanon, 1952 - 1968; F-55-27-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Burnaby Member--Ernest E. Winch (CCF) (4-4) - Letters, statistics, charts, petition. Letters from: Alice Ravenhill, Ernest E. Winch. Includes correspondence with Premier Byron I. Johnson, 1948 - 1955; F-55-27-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Cariboo Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (5-2) - Letters. Letters from: Alfred Smith, J.F. Blenkham, R.S. McIvor, T. Windt, Jack H. Sawatsky, Joan Shaffer, G.M. Kellett, Lillian Walker, 1952 - 1971; F-55-27-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Chilliwack Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (6-2) - Letters. Letters from: M.A. Keyes, Darryl Greveling, R. McKay, Grace L. Morrison, W.H. Leach, Viola Sales, H.L. Klassen, Mrs. E.J. Rempel, J.J. Perdue, Ruby Selmes, Kenneth Kiernan, 1952 - 1970; F-55-27-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Columbia Member--R. Orr Newton (SC) (7-2). - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Richard O. Newton. (File opened 1952.), 1952 - 1963; F-55-27-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Comox Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (7-3) - Letters, telegrams, notes. Letters from: David C. King, William C. Mossman, Mary Paisley, Mary G. James, W.L. Mee, H.J. Champ, C.H. Poole, Harry Harris, Clarence R. Field, 1952 - 1954; F-55-27-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Comox Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (7-3) - Letters. Letters from: David C. King, Mary Paisley, Dan Campbell, Harry Harris, M. Hallgren, 1955 - 1961; F-55-27-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Cowichan Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (7-7) - Letters. Letters from: William C. Mossman, David G. Huntley, W.H. Bryant, H.B. Matthews, B.V. Dunkley, Hazel Fee, Mary Kingston, P.J. Rogers, 1952 - 1967; F-55-27-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Cowichan Member--Robert M. Strachan (CCF) (7-7) - Letters, newspaper clippings, telegram. Letters from: Robert M. Strachan, 1954 - 1961; F-55-27-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Cranbrook Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (7-8) - Let-ters, telegrams, petition. Letters from: Howard C. King, C.S. Andrews, D. Sadler, W.H. Leach, W.L. Fauds, Leo T. Nimsick, Anne Morse, Elvi Miles, Roland J.R. Lambert, 1952 - 1972; F-55-27-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Delta Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (8-1) - Letters, telegrams, newsletters. Letters from: Phyllis McCracken, Menno E. Friesen, Helen L. Lutman, H.A. Langley, F.A. Woolf, Oliver Scott, Donald H. Riggan, Gordon L. Gibson, R.F. Treleaven, R. Houghton, E.C. Proproski, Mary Goggs, Grace L. Morrison, E. Dewhirst, R. Kamla, 1952 - 1972; F-55-27-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Delta Member--Thomas J. Irwin (SC) (8-1) - Letters, telegrams, list. Letters from: Thomas J. Irwin, Percy E. George., 1952 - 1955; F-55-27-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Delta Member--Thomas J. Irwin (SC) (8-1) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Thomas J. Irwin, Willard Ireland, N. George Massey, Gordon L. Gibson, Douglas G. Massey, Lila Massey, 1956 - 1959; F-55-27-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-43)
  - Dewdney Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (8-2) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Raymond G. Inder, J.O. Connell, G.W. Hawkins, H.V. Bird, E.N. Ryall, Marguerite Simpson, Clara Watt, Lockie Miles, 1952 - 1968; F-55-27-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Esquimalt Constituency Association--Social Credit 1952-1970 League, B.C. (9-4) - Letters. Letters from: T.F. Lock, Ethel S. Glenn, Eunice H. Roberts, Stockwell Day, F-55-27-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Finance Minister (10-3) - Budget speech (annotated printed material), news-paper clipping, 1952 - 1953; F-55-27-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Fort George Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (11-3) - Letters, telegram. Letters from: A. Floen, Otto E. Leboe, Percy Kent, R. Hillard Clare, James R. Bellamy, 1953 - 1965; F-55-27-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Fort George Member--Llewellyn L. King (SC) and Ray G. Williston (SC) (11-3) - Letters. Letters from: Llewellyn L. King, 1953 - 1954; F-55-27-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - F Confidential (11-10) - Letters, newsletter. Letters from: Neil M. Fleishman, D.C. Fillmore, Metro Fostey, Leo F. Fielder, E.D. Geoffrey Fuller, R.S.M. Forbes, Hilda Farley, John Fletcher, S.F. Ford, P.H. Frost, K. Sigurd Forsland, H.L. Ford, 1952 - 1955; F-55-27-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Grand Forks Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (13-1) - Letters, newspaper, file note. Letters from: C. Heighton, M.A. Degenstein, L.R. Degenstein, A. Tedesio, Ralph Maida, Gloria Maida, Alfreda M. Huntley, H.H. Rystill, Evonne Cole, O. Ortis, Q. Stephenson, Burt Campbell, 1952 - 1963; F-55-27-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - G Confidential (13-10) - Letters, file note. Letters from: J.A.A. George, John B. Gilman, Harry Giles, Pat Goode, Archie L. Gillis, Einar M. Gunderson, Ronald B. Worley, 1952 - 1956; F-55-27-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Omineca Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (27-3) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Cliff V. Harrison, F.M. Harrison, Twain, 1952 - 1968; F-55-27-0-0-24 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Omineca Member--Cyril M. Shelford (SC) (27-3) - Letters, telegrams, photograph. Letters from: Cyril M. Shelford, 1952 - 1968; F-55-27-0-0-25 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - O Confidential (27-10) - Letters. Letters from: W.J. O'Neill, R.R. Orr, Frank O'Hearn, O. St.P. Aitkens, 1952 - 1954; F-55-27-0-0-26 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Peace River Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (28-1) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Philip Bjorkgren, W.N. Chant, J.A. Moffat, Stan Carnell, J.R. McKenzie, Irma Byrne, J.P. Neufeld, Don Phillips, 1952 - 1966; F-55-27-0-0-27 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Peace River Member--Charles W. Parker (SC) (28-1) - Letters, telegrams - Letters from: Charles W. Parker, Victor Naylor, 1952 - 1957; F-55-27-0-0-28 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Financial report, 1951; F-55-27-0-0-29 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Prince Rupert Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (29-1) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: H. Kraupner, A. Bruce Brown, Lyle Wicks, Jerry L. Horne, 1952 - 1972; F-55-27-0-0-30 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - P Confidential (29-10) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Wilfrid Pocklington, J.E. Paynter, Col. Sir Stanley Paddon, J.W. Phillips, George S. Pearson, J.M. MacLean, Frank Putnam, Frank H. Partridge, William Partridge, 1952 - 1953; F-55-27-0-0-31 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Revelstoke Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (31-3) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Archie D. Oakey, Louis G. Steegstra, Burton P. Campbell, 1952 - 1972; F-55-27-0-0-32 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Revelstoke Member--Vincent Segur (CCF) (31-3) - Letters, map. Letters from: Vincent Segur, Arvid W. Lundell, 1955 - 1956; F-55-27-0-0-33 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Rossland-Trail Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (32-1) - Letters. Letters from: Carl M. Loeblich, F. Delorme, Donald L. Brothers, N.A. Drinnan, Burt Campbell, Florence Grupp, Joe Sutcliffe, 1952 - 1963; F-55-27-0-0-34 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Rossland-Trail Member--Robert E. Sommers (32-1) - Letters, file note. Letters from: G.M.C. Haskell, Robert E. Sommers. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1952 - 1957; F-55-27-0-0-35 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - R Confidential (32-10) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Sam Ross, M.O. Rollefson, C.W. Reeves, Bill Ross, C.E. Rivett-Carnac, R.A. Ramme, John S. Rogers, Alice M. Reynolds, C.W. Reeves, Arvid W. Lundell, 1952 - 1957; F-55-27-0-0-36 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Saanich Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (33-1) - Letters, newsletter. Letters from: R.E. Hyland, A.C. Boydell, John Tisdalle, Lewin Harvey, Thelma Clarke, Carl Bitterman, P.A. Philipchalk, 1952 - 1967; F-55-27-0-0-37 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Saanich Member--Frank Snowsell (CCF) (33-1) - Letters. Letters from: Frank Snowsell. (File opened 1952.), 1953; F-55-27-0-0-38 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Salmon Arm Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (33-2) - Letters. Letters from: M. McClurg, Harold Mason, A.J. Clotworthy, Phyllis M. Hobbs, P.B. Esswein, Emma Coles, 1952 - 1957; F-55-27-0-0-39 (Archival box - standard 55-44)
  - Salmon Arm Member--James A. Reid (SC) (33-2) - Letters, speech. Letters from: D.H. Revel, F. Marr, A.J. Clotworthy, J. Allan Reid, 1952 - 1960; F-55-27-0-0-40 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Similkameen Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (33-3) - Letters, telegrams, note. Letters from: S.A. Hodge, H. Kingsley, W.B. Carter, James R. Christie, John Bowen-Colthurst, H. Schening, 1952 - 1966; F-55-27-0-0-41 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Skeena Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (34-1) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Peer Paynter, Dick Laurence, Wesley D. Black, Philip A. Gaglardi, Robert E. Sommers, Kenneth Kiernan, Hugh Shirreff, Barbara Smith-Hobbs, R. Rapske, J.A. McLean, 1952 - 1960; F-55-27-0-0-42 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Skeena Member--Edward T. Kenney (Lib.) (34-1) - Letters, speech. Letters from: J.E. Bonner, Edward T. Kenney, Frank Howard, 1952 - 1955; F-55-27-0-0-43 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - South Okanagan Constituency Association--Social Credit League, B.C. (34-5) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: E.R. Owen, Coalee Campbell, E. Klingbell, J.E. Chrisholm, Wilda Schuman, C.E. Sladen, L.W. Marr, Milo Sawatsky, Earl Johnson, Robert Van't Hoff, Wayne Wiley, V. Froehlich, 1955 - 1971; F-55-27-0-0-44 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - South Okanagan Member--W.A.C. Bennett (SC) (34-5) - Letters, statement, map, statistics, election expenses. Letters from: D.C. Johnston, E. Ross Oatman, F. Hurley, Coalee Campbell, C.J. Copithorne, F. Hurley, Lloyd A. Miller, 1952 - 1971; F-55-27-0-0-45 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, printed material, letters, 1952 - 1953; F-55-27-0-0-46 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Speeches and Statistics (34-6) - Speeches, notes. (File opened 1952.), 1954; F-55-27-0-0-47 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - S Confidential (34-10) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: F.E. Smith, Ralph Seymour, William Savage, R.S. Scruton, F.O. St. John, B.H. Symns, Frank G. Richards, R.R. Smith, Len Short, William R. Smith, W.H. Stratton, Agnes J.Y. Seeley, Joseph A. Sullivan, Walter J. Smith, John F. Short, P.J. Sinnott, George Stacey, Anna Sprott, 1952 - 1955; F-55-27-0-0-48 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
- 1953 Official files, 1953 - 1972; F-55-28; 11 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened in 1953. Included are correspondence with Members elected in 1953 (years are cumulated), other correspondence, memoranda, a budget, an annual report and income statements.
  - AM-AZ (2) - Political attitude survey, 1953; F-55-28-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Whatshan Power Plant Landslide Damage (3-2) - Letters, telegrams, news-paper clippings. Letters from: J.E. Fitzwater, S.R. Weston, Arthur Laing, George E. Mullen, L.H. Shantz, Henry Murton, Robert W. Bonner. (File opened Aug. 1953.), F-55-28-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - CA-CG (5) - Press releases, 1953; F-55-28-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Esquimalt Member--Herbert J. Bruch (SC) (9-4) - Letters, newsletters. Letters from: H.J. Bruch, Mrs. Herbert Bruch, 1953 - 1972; F-55-28-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Finance Minister (10-3) - Letter. Letters from: Einar M. Gunderson, 1953; F-55-28-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-45)
  - Fort George Member--Ray G. Williston (SC) (11-3) - Letters, telegram, newspaper clippings. Letters from: Adolph Jeck, 1954; F-55-28-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters (carbon copies), pamphlet, 1953; F-55-28-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letter, document, plan, budget, annual report, income statements. Letters from: Ralph Chetwynd, 1953; F-55-28-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - P.G.E. Railway--Willis T. Batcheller (28-2) - Letters, printed material. Letters from: Willis T. Batcheller, 1953; F-55-28-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Provincial Secretary--Minister (Confidential) (29-2) - Letters. Letters from: L.M. Morrison, 1953 - 1961; F-55-28-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Public Works--Minister (Confidential) (29-5) - Letters (carbon copies), telegram, 1953 - 1954; F-55-28-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Saanich Member--John D.T. Tisdalle (SC) (33-1) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: John D.T. Tisdalle. (File opened 1953.), 1954 - 1969; F-55-28-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Similkameen Member--Frank Richter (SC) (33-3) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Frank Richter, Leslie Balla, C.D. Buckland, 1953 - 1960; F-55-28-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Skeena Member--Frank Howard (CCF) (34-1) - Telegrams, letters. Letters from: Frank Howard, 1953 - 1958; F-55-28-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
- 1954 Official files, 1914 - 1963; F-55-29; 25 cm of textual records
  Series consists of the official files of the Premier's Office opened, or continued, in 1954. The records reflect topics such as the B.C. Power Commission, Federal Departments, Finance, International Joint Commission, Oil Pipeline and the P.G.E. Railway. Included are correspondence, financial statements, annual reports, statistics, charts, and press releases.
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Letters, financial statistics, map. Letters from: T.H. Crosby, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-1 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Financial statements, 1954 - 1960; F-55-29-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - B.C. Power Commission (3-2) - Letters, annual report, map. Letters from: T.H. Crosby, H.H. Griffin, Hugh L. Keenleyside, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - BI-BQ (4) -Pamphlet, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Federal-Provincial Conferences--H. Carl Goldenberg (10-1) - Letters, newspaper clippings - Letters from: H. Carl Goldenberg, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Federal Departments (10-1) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Jean Lesage, Robert H. Winters, Einar M. Gunderson. (File opened Jan. 1954.), 1950 - 1954; F-55-29-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Federal Departments (10-1) - Letters, minutes, brief. Letters from: Milton F. Gregg, Paul Martin, Hughes Lapointe, James Sinclair, Ralph Campney, Wesley D. Black, A.B. Patterson, Alistair Fraser, G.W.G. McConachie, Robert W. Bonner, D.C. Abbott, Martin M. Johnson, Stuart Garson, Jean Lesage, 1951 - 1954; F-55-29-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Finance Minister (10-3) - Letters, financial statistics, charts, notes, memorandum, minutes, act, reports, telegrams, financial statement, press releases, newspaper clipping. Letters from: J.V. Fisher, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 55-46)
  - Finance Minister (10-3) - Letters, reports, telegrams, press releases, printed material. Letters from: J.V. Fisher, T.R.B. Adams, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - Finance Minister (10-3) - Pamphlets, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - Finance--Deputy and Department (10-4) - Letters, draft of act, printed material. Letters from: J.V. Fisher., 1954; F-55-29-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - International Joint Commission (16-1) - Memorandum, letters, telegrams, proposal. Letters from: C.K. Hurst, E.M. Sutherland, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - Oil Pipeline--Gas and Gas Prices (27-2) - Letters, telegrams, printed material. Letters from: E.A. Evans, S.A. Wallace, J.E. Fitzwater, G. Spratt, Ray C. Fish, R.H.C. Harrison, Derick E. Oliver, S. Blain, T.W.G. Thomson, T.C. Twyman, D.P. McDonald, Lloyd K. Turner, John A. McMaiton, George Hahn, Anthony E. Loscalzo, Cecil Dodds, Murray Doyle, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - Oil Pipeline--Gas and Gas Prices (27-2) - Brief, annual report, printed material, letters. Letters from: G. Spratt, D.P. McDonald, 1950 - 1954; F-55-29-0-0-14 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters, reports, financial statistics. Letters from: Archie Carter, William A. Laming, D.G. Kilburn, Robert W. Bonner, Ed Meade, T.H. Crosby, Ralph Chetwynd, G.S. Bryson, H.S. Taylor, L.R. Andrews, William E. Grant, J.A. Young, R.F.P. Bowman, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters, speech, press release, reports. Letters from: Ralph Chetwynd, A.M. Clark, R.F.P. Bowman, J.L. Whitehead, R.L. Duchossois, E.E. Protheroe, Robert F. Lyons, R.F.P. Bowman, R.M. Burns, E. Kennedy, Robert E. Sommers, Laurie Corkhum, Robert D. Harvey, Charles R. Lee, Thomas Jamieson, H.A. Schieve, J. Smith, F. Griffiths, Ernie Plant, J.V. Fisher, F. O'Sullivan, K.M. Richardson, C.D. Schultz, Eric Yorston, R.A. Seitz, P.A. Gibbs, John W. Barlee, Harold Roberts, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Financial statements, budgets, letter. Letters from: R.F.P. Bowman, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - P.G.E. Railway (28-2) - Letters, report, document (copy). Letters from: D. McNair, Ralph Chetwynd, R.F.P. Bowman. (File designated "Premier's Safe".), 1914 - 1954; F-55-29-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 55-47)
  - P.G.E. Extension File (28-2) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: G.H. Kidd, K.R. Moffat, Renee Ronayne, Tracy Emerson, E.S.B. Conolly, Edward Coldicott, Perry Livingstone, M.G.K. Stuart, Bill Hilton, Walter R. Hamilton, Robert W. Thompson, Ernie Plant, L.C. Pimm, John F. Latta, John P. Clement, Elmer Nelson, Peter Edmark, C.E. Scanlan, H.H. German, Angus M. MacDonald, R.C. Gibbs, George Hahn, Robert M. Strachan, K.C. Harris, W. Hay, L.G. Mayer, T.M. Stephen, C.R. Smith, C.B. Touchbourn, Charles B. Brown, A.H. Ray, R.A. Harrison, Phyllis K. Norminton, J.A. Wood, Samuel Fulton, W.D.. Adair, E. Unger, S. Smith, Jack Loutet, John S. George, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - P.G.E. Extension File (28-2) - Letters, telegrams. Letters from: Margery F. Alger, G.G. Clarke, Arthur Laing, Lester A. Halpin, Edward W. Green, Henry Ayling, T.P. Masters, William Franklin Wolsey, Ada M. Dyrsmid, Anne Eleanor Jones, Percy Adair, Jack Coutet, Frank Wilson, W.B. Carter, Edward Weir, J. C. Mehain, E.C. Leavitt, A.D. MacLean, Ada Helliwell, R.R. Shilling, John Anderson, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - P.G.E. Extension File (28-2)- Letters. Letters from: Ella Davis, Jack K. Melville, H.S. Chambers, L. McDonnell, Harvey R. Carson, M.A. Lundeen, Tracey Emerson, J.H. Stewart, C.M. Campbell, J.W. Gard, W.E. Ross, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - SA-SI (33) - Press excerpt, 1948; F-55-29-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 55-48)
  - Speeches, Reports, etc.--Mimeographed (34-7) - Interview notes, 1954; F-55-29-0-0-23 (Archival box - standard 55-48)